ABDULLAH MOHAMED KAMAL

212 Ard El-mazad St, Fifth District, October City · 00201119620206 <u>abdalla.m.kamal@gmail.com</u>

ABAP consultant with 5 years of experience in developing ABAP reports, screen, forms and enhancements to meet business requirements. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into role as ABAP consultant

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Born august 13, 1993 in Giza (Egypt)

Citizenship: EgyptMarital status: Single

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abdullah-mohamed-56ba79101

EXPERIENCE

7 / 2022 – Present
ABAP TEAM LEADER, ATOS EGYPT

• 3 / 2021 – 7 / 2022 SENIOR ABAP CONSULTANT, B-CONNECT

1 / 2019 – 3/2021
ABAP CONSULTANT, EDRAKY

1 / 2018 – 1/ 2019
ABAP CONSULTANT, ECC

1 / 2016 – 1 / 2017
TEACHER ASSISTANAT, 6TH OF OCTOBER UNIVERSITY

EDUCATION

• 2011-2015

BECHOLOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, 6TH OF OCTOBER UNIVERSITY

GPA: 3.27

Grade: very good

SKILLS

- Data dictionary
- Modularization
- ALV report
- Batch data communication
- Module pool programming
- Enhancement
- Adobe interactive forms
- Object oriented programming
- Workflow
- Web service
- PROAXIA integration
- Scale integration (Serial port)
- SAPUI5 Development

PROJECTS

- Support
 - EMISAL: Egyptian company for salt production
 - ASK: Drywall products and systems for partitions, ceilings manufacturing
 - Nile Air: Egyptian private airline offering integrated services in the field of air transport
 - Fly Egypt: Egyptian private airline offering integrated services in the field of air transport
 - **ELSALLAB**: Market leaders in the ceramics tile trade
 - **FLO**: Alkaline water company
 - IWAN: Real estate development company
 - AAV: Military and civilian vehicles assemble company
 - Ghalioungi: Marketing and sale of specialized medical and surgical products
 - Hoshan Holding: Trading, commerce, manufacturing, real estate, and financial services
 - Lapoire: One of the best pastry chains in Egypt
 - MAGRABI: The eyewear leader offering fashion-focused experience for women, men, and kids
 - **Pharmaplast**: Leader in global wound care and cosmetics products
 - **Zeina**: Egyptian company for paper, tissue & hygienic products.
 - **TAQA**: Egyptian company for gas distribution and renewable power generation.
 - HESNI: One of leading textile companies in Egypt
- Full Implementation
 - **UBM**: United biomed for pharmaceutical & biological industries
 - Atrium: Talaat Mustafa Group's construction arm specializing in residential projects
 - **Towngas**: Egyptian company for gas distribution
 - El-garhy Steel: Egyptian company working in the field of reinforcing steel
 - Mitsubishi: Power generation services and equipment supplier
 - IDH: Leading consumer healthcare company in the Middle East and Africa
 - EIM: Egyptian international motors for servicing and distribution of automotive vehicles
 - Geidea: Information Technology Solutions (KSA)
 - **UCP**: The co-leader of the Egyptian pharmaceutical distribution market
 - EGYPTGAS: Egypt Gas is the major operating corporation in Natural Gas Distribution EPC-based Projects